Guide to the University Marshal records, 1825-2005 RG0043
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs and addresses, 1826-2005; RG0043 Series 2; 7.5 Linear feet (Box 12, Box 14, Box 4, Box 1, Box 15, Box 3, Box 2, Box 11, Box 9, Box 10, Box 7, Box 8, Box 5, Box 6)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/12/1940 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1941 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/11/1941 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/23/1942 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/03/1942 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1943 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 06/02/1943 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/17/1943 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1944 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 05/31/1944 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 09/19/1944 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1945 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/30/1945 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/17/1945 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1946 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 05/29/1946 (Box 2, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/15/1946 (Box 2, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1947 (Box 2, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 05/28/1947 (Box 2, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/11/1947 (Box 2, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/23/1948 (Box 2, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 05/26/1948 (Box 2, Folder 42)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 11/11/1948 (Box 2, Folder 43)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1949 (Box 2, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/01/1949 (Box 2, Folder 45)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 11/11/1949 (Box 2, Folder 46)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1950 (Box 2, Folder 47)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 05/31/1950 (Box 2, Folder 48)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/11/1950 (Box 2, Folder 49)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1951 (Box 2, Folder 50)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 05/30/1951 (Box 2, Folder 51)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/12/1951 (Box 2, Folder 52)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1952 (Box 2, Folder 53)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 05/28/1952 (Box 2, Folder 54)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/11/1952 (Box 2, Folder 55)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1953 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 05/27/1953 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/11/1953 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1954 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/09/1954 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 11/11/1954 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1955 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium (rain location), 06/08/1955 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/15/1955 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1956 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/06/1956 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/20/1956 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1957 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/05/1957 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/19/1957 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1958 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/04/1958 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/18/1958 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/23/1959 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/03/1959 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/17/1959 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1960 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/01/1960 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/22/1960 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1961 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/07/1961 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 10/21/1961 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 02/22/1962 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/06/1962 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/21/1963 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/05/1963 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1964 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/07/1964 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1965 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/06/1965 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/21/1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/05/1966 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1967 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/04/1967 (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1968 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/02/1968 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/22/1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, University Yard, 06/08/1969 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/21/1970 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/31/1970 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/15/1971 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/30/1971 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/21/1972 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Theatre, 05/14/1972 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/19/1973 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Theatre, 05/06/1973 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, Constitution Hall, 02/18/1974 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Theatre, 05/05/1974 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, DAR Constitution Hall, 02/17/1975 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Theatre, 05/04/1975 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/16/1976 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Center, 05/09/1976 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/21/1977 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Center, 05/08/1977 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/20/1978 (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, Dorothy Betts Marvin Center, 05/07/1978 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/19/1979 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/06/1979 (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/18/1980 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/04/1980 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/16/1981 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/03/1981 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/15/1982 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/09/1982 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/21/1983 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/08/1983 (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/20/1984 (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/06/1984 (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/17/1985 (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/05/1985 (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/16/1986 (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/04/1986 (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/10/1987 (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/14/1988 (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/08/1988 (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/19/1989 (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/07/1989 (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/18/1990 (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/03/1990 (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/17/1991 (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/12/1991 (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/16/1992 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/10/1992 (Box 6, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 02/14/1993 (Box 6, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Program, Program, 05/09/1993 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/08/1994 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/14/1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/19/1996 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/18/1997 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/17/1998 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/16/1999 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/21/2000 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/20/2001 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/19/2002 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/18/2003 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Program, The Ellipse, 05/16/2004 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Program, 05/22/2005 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Program, 05/21/06 (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Program, 05/20/2007 (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Program, 05/18/2008 (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Program, 05/17/2009 (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Programs, 2010-2014 (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, 03/04/1874 (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, 03/21/1878 (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Program, 03/20/1879 (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Program, 03/18/1880 (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Program, 03/17/1881 (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Program, 03/20/1884 (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Albaugh's Opera House, 05/03/1894 (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/31/1960 (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/31/1970 (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/30/1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/28/1972 (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/27/1973 (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/26/1974 (Box 9, Folder 13)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/23/1975 (Box 9, Folder 14)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/21/1976 (Box 9, Folder 15)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/27/1977 (Box 9, Folder 16)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/26/1978 (Box 9, Folder 17)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/25/1979 (Box 9, Folder 18)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/23/1980 (Box 9, Folder 19)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/29/1981 (Box 9, Folder 20)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/28/1982 (Box 9, Folder 21)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/27/1983 (Box 9, Folder 22)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/25/1984 (Box 9, Folder 23)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/24/1985 (Box 9, Folder 24)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/30/1986 (Box 9, Folder 25)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/29/1987 (Box 9, Folder 26)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/27/1988 (Box 9, Folder 27)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/26/1989 (Box 9, Folder 28)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/25/1990 (Box 9, Folder 29)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/31/1991 (Box 9, Folder 30)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, 05/29/1992 (Box 9, Folder 31)
  - Medical School Commencement Program, 04/02/1993 (Box 9, Folder 32)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Congregational Church, 06/10/1868 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Congregational Church, 06/10/1869 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Congregational Church, 06/12/1872 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Lincoln Hall, 06/10/1874 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Untitled, 06/09/1875 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Untitled, 06/14/1876 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Law School Commencement Program, National Theatre, 06/03/1884 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Law School Commencement Program, New National Theatre, 06/07/1887 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Law School Commencement Program, New National Theatre, 06/12/1888 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Law School Commencement Program, The Academy of Music, 06/09/1891 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Law School Commencement Program, New National Theatre, 06/07/1892 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Law School Commencement Program, The Academy of Music, 06/13/1893 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Law School Commencement Program, The Academy of Music, 06/12/1894 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Law School Commencement Program, The Academy of Music, 06/11/1895 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Law School Commencement Program, New National Theatre, 06/08/1897 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 06/08/1969 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 06/04/1972 (Box 10, Folder 17)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/26/1974 (Box 10, Folder 18)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/23/1976 (Box 10, Folder 19)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/22/1977 (Box 10, Folder 20)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/21/1978 (Box 10, Folder 21)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/20/1979 (Box 10, Folder 22)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/18/1980 (Box 10, Folder 23)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/24/1981 (Box 10, Folder 24)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/23/1982 (Box 10, Folder 25)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Lisner Auditorium, 05/22/1983 (Box 10, Folder 26)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/20/1984 (Box 10, Folder 27)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/19/1985 (Box 10, Folder 28)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/18/1986 (Box 10, Folder 29)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/17/1987 (Box 10, Folder 30)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/22/1988 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/21/1989 (Box 10, Folder 32)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 05/20/1990 (Box 10, Folder 33)
  - Law School Commencement Program, Charles E. Smith Center, 06/02/1991 (Box 10, Folder 34)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/31/1992 (Box 10, Folder 35)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/29/1994 (Box 10, Folder 36)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/28/1995 (Box 10, Folder 37)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/25/1997 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/30/1999 (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/28/2000 (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/27/2001 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/26/2002 (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/25/2003 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Law School Commencement Program, 05/23/2004 (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Commencement Address by Herbert Putnam, 06/03/1903 (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - Commencement Address by Justice Brewster, 02/22/1905 (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - Commencement Address by various, 02/22/1909 (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - Commencement Address by US Attorney General Wickersham, 02/22/1910 (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - Commencement Address by Wendell Stafford, 06/07/1916 (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - Commencement Address by James Phinney Munroe, 02/22/1918 (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - Commencement Address by James Wadsworth, 02/22/1919 (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - Commencement Address by Senator Poindexter (among others), 10/02/1919 (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - Commencement Address by British Ambassador, and Pres. Collier and Prof. Stafford, 05/31/1920 (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - Commencement Address by Huston Thompson, 06/07/1922 (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - Commencement Address by John Garland Pollard, 02/22/1923 (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - Commencement Address by John Merriam, 02/22/1924 (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - Commencement Address by Charles Warren, 02/22/1927 (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Commencement Address by President Coolidge, 02/22/1929 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - Commencement Address by Cloyd Marvin, 06/01/1949 (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Commencement Address by Robert Whitney Bolwell, 02/22/1952 (Box 11, Folder 16)
  - Commencement Address by Henry Grattan Doyle, 11/11/1953 (Box 11, Folder 17)
  - Commencement Address by Elmer Louis Kayser, 06/06/1956 (Box 11, Folder 18)
  - Commencement Address by Jams Webb, 06/07/1961 (Box 11, Folder 19)
  - Commencement Address by Calvin Darlington Linton, 10/21/1961 (Box 11, Folder 20)
  - Commencement Address by Glenn Seaborg, 06/06/1962 (Box 11, Folder 21)
  - Commencement Address by William Foster, 02/21/1963 (Box 11, Folder 22)
  - Commencement Address by John McCormack, 02/22/1964 (Box 11, Folder 23)
  - Commencement Address by Elmer Louis Kayser, 06/04/1967 (Box 11, Folder 24)
  - Commencement Address by Earl Warren, 02/22/1969 (Box 11, Folder 25)
  - Commencement Address by Mayor W. Washington, 02/21/1970 (Box 11, Folder 26)
  - Commencement Address by Julius Axelrod, 02/15/1971 (Box 11, Folder 27)
  - Commencement Address by Ronald Berman, 05/05/1974 (Box 11, Folder 28)
  - Commencement Address by David Lloyd Kreeger, 02/16/1976 (Box 11, Folder 29)
  - Commencement Address by Sen. Mark Hatfield and student Rasario Beringueluy, 05/09/1976 (Box 11, Folder 30)
  - Commencement Address by Dr. Bernard Knox, 02/21/1977 (Box 11, Folder 31)
  - Commencement Address by Ambassador of Sri Lanka, 02/20/1978 (Box 11, Folder 32)
  - Commencement Address by Lee Iacocca, Lisle C. Carter, Colin Turnbull, Scott Levin, 05/06/1979 (Box 11, Folder 33)
  - Commencement Address by Sen. Charles Mathias Jr., 02/16/1981 (Box 11, Folder 34)
  - Commencement Address by Student J. Antonio Endoso to Senior Class, 06/03/1905 (Box 11, Folder 35)
  - Commencement Address by Ruth Simmons, 05/19/2002 (Box 11, Folder 36)
  - Commencement Address by Gov. Mark Warner, 05/18/2003 (Box 11, Folder 37)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by John Ordronaux, 03/06/1867 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Profs. Antisell and Newlands, 03/02/1871 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Bolls, and Gassoway, 03/07/1872 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, King, and Bremerman, 03/04/1874 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Drinkard, and Johnston, 03/11/1875 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Fristoe and Dana, 03/09/1876 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Johnston, and Ball, 03/15/1877 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Lee, and Lewis, 03/21/1878 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Thompson, and Pool, 03/20/1879 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Welling, Coues, and Maddox, 03/18/1880 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Fristoe and Bennett, 03/17/1881 (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Profs. Johnston and McLauglin, 03/16/1882 (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. King and Wales, 03/15/1883 (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs Lee and Harris, 03/20/1884 (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Prof. Elliott Coues and Leonard K. Graves, 03/18/1885 (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Drs. Gooding and Cissel, 03/17/1886 (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Elliott Coues (bound edition), 03/16/1887 (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Dr. D.W. Prentiss, 03/17/1892 (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Ward Darley, 09/16/1957 (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Medical School Commencement Address by Donald S. Fredrickson, 05/24/1985 (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Robert S. Hale, 06/12/1872 (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Law School Commencement Address by William Strong, 06/09/1885 (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Samuel Shellabarger, 06/08/1886 (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Alexander B. Hagner, 06/07/1887 (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Leon Jaworski, 05/26/1974 (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Mortimer Caplin, 05/21/1978 (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Wade H. McCree, 05/20/1979 (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Sam Brown, 05/18/1980 (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Warren Burger, 05/24/1981 (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Judge Harold H. Greene, 05/19/1985 (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - Law School Commencement Address by Mayor Sharon Pratt Dixon, 06/02/1991 (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Law School Commencement Address by George Mitchell, 05/26/2002 (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Other School addresses--School of Public and International Affairs Commencement Address by J.A. Robinson, 05/08/1977 (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Other School addresses--School of Education and Human Development Commencement Address by Dave Darland, 05/08/1977 (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Other School addresses--School of Government and Business Administration Commencement Address by Dean Peter, 05/07/1978 (Box 13, Folder 3)